When running a loop, you may need to change
the code that displays for a loop iteration,
as we have seen with the break or continue
statement. Still, as you build an app, you may not
know what code is needed in a certain spot and may
want to leave a placeholder for possible code to
add later. The Pass keyword is that placeholder.
Pass is unlike the break or continue keywords,
as it does not break out of a loop or pause a
loop. To see how pass works in the context of
a loop, I will, in this 225-pass file, replace the
print statement, on line 5, with a pass statement,
as the game testers are not sure if the message
in place is correct. I will leave the continue
statement in so that the print statement on line 7
runs for the other coins. Let’s run this code. As
expected, the coins that are not platinum printed.
Pass is valuable because it allows one to build
parts of code while waiting for information and
thus continue to structure code without waiting
unnecessarily, saving overall time in building
apps. After all, having a framework and filling
in details is much more efficient than waiting
on information before even building a framework.